Finding Aid for the Collection of 78rpm Sound Discs PASC-M.0174
UCLA Library Special Collections
Collection of 78rpm sound discs
1910-1960
UCLA Library Special Collections
PASC-M.0174
513.5 Linear Feet (1027 boxes)
Archival collection of 78 rpm sound recordings. The collection is in the midst of being processed. The finding aid will be updated periodically.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Audio material partially processed.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9934670783606533
Scope and Content
Archival collection of 78 rpm gramophone records housed in the UCLA Music Library, Archive of Popular American Music. General collection, Box 1 - 263, 280 - 299, 303 - 304, 339 - 347/Jazz recordings, Box 264 - 274, 305 - 338/Wolcott gift, Box 275 - 279/Silbaugh gift, Box 300 - 302
The collection is organized into the following series:
Series 1. General Collection
Series 3. Cal State Long Beach Gift
Series 4. Eselun Gift
Series 5. Harry James Sound Recording Collection
Series 6. Silbaugh Gift
Series 7. Ken Stone Gift
Series 8. Kelmer Gift
Series 9. Walter Collection
Series 10. Wolcott Gift
- General Collection, Series 1.
  Scope and Contents note
  This series consists of 78 rpm sound recordings which cannot be attributed to any one specific archival collection.
  Arrangement note
  Items are arranged by song title, and by label and issue number within each box.
  - Popular Music Recordings, Subseries 1.
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 3)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 4)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 5)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 6)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 7)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 8)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 9)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 10)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 11)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 12)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 13)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 14)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 15)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 16)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 17)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 18)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 19)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 20)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 21)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 22)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 23)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 24)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 25)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 26)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 27)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 28)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 29)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 30)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 31)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 32)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 33)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 34)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 35)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 36)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 37)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 38)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 39)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 40)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 41)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 42)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 43)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 44)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 45)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 46)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 47)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 48)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 49)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 50)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 51)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 52)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 53)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 54)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 55)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 56)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 57)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 58)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 59)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 60)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 61)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 62)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 63)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 64)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 65)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 66)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 67)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 68)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 69)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 70)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 71)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 72)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 73)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 74)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 75)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 76)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 77)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 78)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 79)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 80)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 81)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 82)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 83)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 84)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 85)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 86)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 87)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 88)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 89)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 90)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 91)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 92)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 93)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 94)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 95)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 96)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 97)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 98)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 99)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 100)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 101)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 102)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 103)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 104)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 105)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 106)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 107)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 108)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 109)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 110)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 111)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 112)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 113)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 114)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 115)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 116)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 117)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 118)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 119)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 120)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 121)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 122)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 123)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 124)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 125)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 126)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 127)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 128)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 129)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 130)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 131)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 132)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 133)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 134)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 135)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 136)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 137)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 138)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 139)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 140)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 141)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 142)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 143)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 144)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 145)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 146)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 147)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 148)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 149)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 150)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 151)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 152)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 153)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 154)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 155)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 156)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 157)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 158)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 159)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 160)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 161)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 162)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 163)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 164)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 165)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 166)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 167)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 168)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 169)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 170)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 171)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 172)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 173)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 174)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 175)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 176)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 177)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 178)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 179)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 180)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 181)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 182)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 183)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 184)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 185)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 186)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 187)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 188)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 189)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 190)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 191)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 192)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 193)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 194)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 195)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 196)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 197)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 198)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 199)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 200)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 201)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 202)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 203)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 204)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 205)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 206)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 207)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 208)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 209)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 210)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 211)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 212)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 213)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 214)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 215)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 216)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 217)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 218)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 219)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 220)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 221)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 222)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 223)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 224)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 225)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 226)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 227)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 228)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 229)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 230)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 231)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 232)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 233)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 234)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 235)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 236)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 237)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 238)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 239)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 240)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 241)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 242)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 243)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 244)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 245)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 246)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 247)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 248)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 249)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 250)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 251)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 252)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 253)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 254)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 255)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 256)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 257)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 258)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 259)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 260)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 261)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 262)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 263)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 280)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 281)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 282)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 283)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 284)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 285)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 286)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 287)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 288)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 289)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 290)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 291)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 292)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 293)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 294)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 295)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 296)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 297)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 298)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 299)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 303)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 304)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 339)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 340)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 341)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 342)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 343)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 344)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 345)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 346)
    - Unprocessed Recordings (Box 347)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 662)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 662)
    - Assorted Unprocessed 78s (Box 663)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 664)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 665)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 666)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 667)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 668)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 669)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 670)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 671)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 672)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 673)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 674)
    - Assorted Unprocessed 20th Century Fox Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 675)
    - Assorted Unprocessed 20th Century Fox Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 676)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 677)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 678)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 682)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 683)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 684)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 685)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 686)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 687)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 688)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 689)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 690)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 691)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 692)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 693)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 694)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 695)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 696)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 697)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 698)
    - Assorted Unprocessed 20th Century Fox Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 699)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 699)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 700)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 701)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 702)
    - Assorted Unprocessed 20th Century Fox Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 703)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 704)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 709)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 710)
    - Assorted Unprocessed 20th Century Fox Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 711)
    - Assorted Unprocessed 20th Century Fox Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 712)
    - Assorted Unprocessed 20th Century Fox Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 713)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 714)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 715)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 716)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 717)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 718)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 719)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 720)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 721)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 722)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 723)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 724)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 725)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 727)
      General note
      Album covers in Box 765
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 728)
      Album covers in Box 766
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 729)
      Album covers in Box 767
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 730)
      Album covers in Box 768
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 731)
      Album covers in Box 769
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 732)
      Album covers in Box 770
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 733)
      Album covers in Box 771
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 734)
      Album covers in Box 772
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 735)
      Album covers in box 773
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 736)
      Album covers in Box 774
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 737)
      Album covers in Box 775
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 738)
      Album covers in Box 776
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 739)
      Album covers in Box 777
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 740)
      Album covers in Box 778
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 741)
      Album covers in Box 779
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 742)
      Album covers in Box 780
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 743)
      Album covers in Box 781
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 744)
      Albums covers in Box 782
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 745)
      Album covers in Box 783
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 746)
      Album covers in Box 784
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 747)
      Album covers in Box 785
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 748)
      Album covers in box 786
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 749)
      Album covers in Box 787
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 750)
      Album covers in Box 788
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 751)
      Album covers in Box 789
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 752)
      Album covers in Box 790
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 753)
      Album covers in Box 791
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 754)
      Album covers in Box 792
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 755)
      Album covers in Box 793
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 756)
      Album covers in Box 794
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 762)
      Album covers in Box 795
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 763)
      Album covers in Box 796
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 764)
      Album covers in Box 797
    - Assorted Unprocessed Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 765)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 798)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 799)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 800)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 801)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 802)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 804)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 805)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 806)
    - Assorted Unprocessed MGM and RCA Non-Commercial sound discs (Box 828)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 829)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 830)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 831)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 832)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 833)
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 834)
      Edison discs
    - Assorted Unprocessed 78s (Box 835)
    - Assorted Unprocessed 78s (Box 836)
    - Assorted Unprocessed 78s (Box 837)
    - Assorted Unprocessed 78s (Box 838)
    - Assorted Unprocessed 78s (Box 839)
    - Assorted Unprocessed 78s (Box 840)
    - Assorted Unprocessed 78s (Box 841)
    - Assorted Unprocessed 78s (Box 842)
    - Assorted Unprocessed 78s (Box 843)
    - Assorted Unprocessed 78s (Box 844)
    - Assorted Unprocessed 78s (Box 845)
    - Assorted Unprocessed 78s (Box 846)
    - Assorted Unprocessed 78s (Box 847)
    - Assorted Unprocessed 78s (Box 848)
    - After All, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: A 2704, side 1
    - All for Love, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 20 1555 A
      Also composed by: Whitcup, Schuster and Rosenberg.
    - Ba Ba Lu, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: C 1167 a
    - La Bohemia, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 40163 B
    - Carolina Moon, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 826 H, side 1
      Also composed by: Burke.
    - Clover Blossoms, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 14281 A
    - Cross Roads, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 778 H, side 2
      Also composed by: Mendoza and Klages. On label, "from "Show People"."
    - Da Da Da My Darling (Box 348)
    - Da Da Da My Darling, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: A 3521, side 1
    - Dapper Dan, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: A 3477, side 1
    - Ding A Ring A Ring, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: A 3375, side 2
    - Do You Know (Medley), 1918; 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 10197, side 2
      Also composed by: Fitzgibbon, Hickman and Black.
    - Don't Cry Frenchy, Don't Cry, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: A 2704, side 2
    - Dream of Heaven, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 14281 B
    - Easy Melody, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 14170 B
      Also composed by: Rodemich.
    - Easy to Love, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 20 1555 B
    - Ebb Tide, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 1358, side 2
    - Gone But Still in My Heart, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 14120 A
    - The Heart of a Girl, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 12155, side 2
      Also composed by: Spitalny.
    - He's Had No Lovin' For a Long, Long Time, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 18546 B
      Also composed by: Conrad and Fuller.
    - Hilo March, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 10187, side 1
    - Holiday for Strings, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 23311 A
    - Home Again Blues, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: A 3375, side 1
      Also composed by: Akst.
    - I Apologize, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 1699 A
      Also composed by: Goodhart and Nelson.
    - I Can't Give You Anything But Love, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 660 H, side 1
      On label, "from "Blackbirds of 1928"."
    - I Don't Care What You Used to Be (I Know What You Are Today), 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: 12155, side 1
    - I Gave You Up Just Before You Threw Me Down, 1 10" sound disc (Box 348)
      Publisher no.: B 14513
      Also composed by: Ruby and Kalmar.